colwayinternational.com 2017-06-07

# In the case of Registered Clients, their personal data are also available to the Company's

                                          PRIVACY POLICY –
                                   TERMS OF PURCHASE (extract)
                                         § VII Personal data
1. The Company acts as the personal data administrator.
2. The User’s personal data are processed in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of 29
   August 1997 and the Act of 18 July 2002 on electronically provided services, regardless of whether
   such services are provided in relation to personal data sets. Data submission is voluntary.
3. Upon the Product sale or User registration, the User’s personal data are stored in the Company’s
   personal database. The data are processed in order to enter into, develop the content of, and
   perform the agreement for the sale of Products, or in order to amend or terminate such an
   agreement.
4. The Company will use the data provided by the User for purposes related to the administration of
   the User’s account (upon registration), review and execution of the financial transactions related
   to online payments, as well as monitoring the process of downloading data from the Company’s
   website, improving the layout and/or content of the Company’s website and adapting it to User
   needs, registration of Users with the Company's website and conducting demographic studies
   relating to Users.
5. The Company is authorised to provide the User’s name, surname and address, telephone number
   and email address to a third party in order to supply the Product to the User (for example, to a
   courier company or another supplier).
1. In every competition, the Company uses the data to contact the winners. For more information,
   the User should read the terms of participation in the competition concerned.
2. When placing an order or going through a registration procedure, the User may additionally
   express their consent to the processing of personal data for marketing purposes, including the
   sending of newsletters and commercial information, to the email address and/or mobile phone
   number provided by the User. The User’s consent to receive commercial information may be
   revoked at any time.
3. In the case of Registered Clients, their personal data are also available to the Company's
   sales Partner who has recommended the Company’s products.
4. The User has the right to inspect their personal data and to request the correction and/or deletion
   of the data. The User may correct the data themselves through data editing in the User’s profile at
   colwayinternational.com.
                                 § VIII Data collected automatically
1. The Company hereby informs the User that when they connect to the Company’s website their
   personal information is collected and stored, or the information already stored in the User’s
   communication device is accessed – a fact of which the User is also notified each time they visit
   the Company’s online shop. The data are collected automatically during the User’s visit to the
   website, and they include information on the IP address, domain name, browser type, operating
   system type, etc. These data are not personal data.
2. The User’s information is stored and accessed on the spot so that the Company may analyse the
   Users’ behaviours during their visit to the website or collect demographic information relating to
   the Users and fulfil their orders.

3. After receiving information on the automatic collection of data, i.e. “Cookies”, the User may give
   their consent for such data to be stored and accessed by the Company, or they may define the
   storage and access terms for Cookies (including the refusal to allow Cookies) using the settings of
   the software installed by the User on their communication device (e.g. a computer). Every web
   browser has the option of automatic rejection of Cookies.
4. Cookies do not affect the operation of the User’s telecommunication equipment in an adverse
   manner, nor do they change the configuration of the device or any software installed on it.
